

IHOR CHASTKOVSKYI Kyiv, Ukraine

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

CONTACTS

- (050) 989-71-79
- 🔼 <u>chasigor@gmail.com</u>
- in linkedin.com/in/ihor-chastkovskyi
- instagram.com/ihorchastkovskii/

SKILLS

C++

GitHub

Linux/Unix

HTML

Software Development

Tava

SOL

Science

Cognitive behavioura

psvchotherapy

LANGUAGES

English Intermedia

Ukrainian Native

Russian Native

Summary

Graduated 10 years ago and looking for an oportunity to come back into IT. I have a good educational background and some basic programming skills but a lack of expierience. At student years i was passioned in researches of cognitive processes and brain modeling. Learning my sychology to create thinking and understanding machines with own World model. It transformed into interest to psychology and psychotherapy so i'm a kinda emphatic person.

Started C++ GlobalLogic BaseCamp but it was interrupted by war:(

Now i'm on my way to Software Developer position.

Employment History

NO COMMERTIAL EXPIERIENCE

IT Courses teacher at ITStolytsa.ua

Jan 2016 - Oct 2016

- Teaching Computer Basics and C++

Automatisation engineer at Military Forces of Ukraine

Jun 2017 - Dec 2018

- -Engineer support of military Anti-Aircraft stations
- -Administration of Windows systems
- -Office work

Education

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

Master's degree, Computer Science 2006 – 2012

C++ GL BaseCamp at GlobalLogicEducation

Stopped Because of War, February 2022

Interests

Thinking
Philosophy
Psychology
Cognitive behavioural therapy
Brain modeling
Cooking
Instagram